

UDISHI VERMA

- 🗣 K2, Pragati Nagar, Near Florence Apartments, Kotra, 305001 Ajmer, India
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/udishi-verma-00b8301bb/

PROFILE

I am a proactive digital marketing enthusiast, with reliable command over SEO and Keyword Analysis, well equipped with the domains of social media, content writing and business communication. I am keen to understand customer behavior and plan marketing strategies for growing firms. I have sufficient knowledge of excel, presentations, and a strong vocabulary and can handle tense client situations with patience. My past experience has given me a rousing understanding of various marketing channels, commerce platforms, marketing approaches and leading campaigns, deciding on strategies, next posts and making strategies with teams.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MARKETING INTERN

March 2022 - April 2022

Western Oranges Z

New Delhi

- Managed Official Instagram Handle of Le Fréur, the coffee brand of Western Oranges.
- Led and coordinated with the Marketing Campaign Team.
- Performed Analysis on Instagram Insights.
- Increased the organic followers count by 100%.
- Optimized Site Content to Maximize Organic Traffic.
- Designed Amazon A+ Creative Modules for Le Fréur products.
- Received a *Letter of Recommendation* ☑ for this internship.

SHOPIFY CONTENT WRITER AND SEO ANALYST

July 2021 - February 2022

Spike Fitness 🖸

- Wrote Articles on Fitness Products and Physical Well-being.
- Added **Backlinks** and **Interlinks** to Internal and External Websites.
- Performed **Keyword Research** for each Article.
- Worked Dedicated under a Team Ensuring Good Quality Content.
- Performed **Proof Reading**.
- Published Articles on **Shopify**.
- Performed SEO Analysis for Maximizing Traffic to Blogs.
- Wrote **YouTube Descriptions** for various products offered.
- Received a *Letter of Recommendation* of for this internship.

CONTENT WRITER AND SOCIAL MEDIA ANALYST

July 2020 -December 2020

- Wrote Articles on **Social Media Marketing** and **Affiliate Marketing**.

Mumbai

- Gave each article innovative thoughts.
- Performed **Proof Reading** for Quality Standards.
- Worked with MS Office.
- Reviewed Products.
- Backlinks, Keyword Research in Social Media Marketing.
- Received a *Letter of Recommendation* of for this internship.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S OF COMMERCE

2019 - 2022

Sophia Girls' College (Autonomous)

Ajmer, India

HIGH SCHOOL

2005 - 2019

Sophia Sr, Sec. School Ajmer, India

CERTIFICATES

Digital Marketing Training ☑ (Internshala Trainings)

Internship and Job Preparation (Internshala Trainings)

Social Media Marketing (Edelytics)

Google Search Certification (Google Skillshop)

SKILLS

Search Engine Optimization

Keyword Analysis

Blog Writing

Microsoft Excel

Communication Skills

Microsoft Word

Proof Reading

Social Media Management

Digital Marketing

Shopify Blog Writing

PowerPoint Presentations

Team Work

LETTERS OF RECOMMENDATION

Letter of Recommendation

Singh John

Received LOR for exceptional performance at Singh John.

Letter of Recommendation 2

Spike Fitness

Received LOR for good work ethics and exemplary skills at Spike Fitness.



Poems

Dancing

Yoga

Spirituality

Reading

Popular Mythologies



LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

French